export const lvl10 = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: `What is the primary mode of public transport in Brisbane?`,
    answers: [`A) Trains`, `B) Buses`, `C) Ferries`],
    correctAnswer: `A) Trains`,
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: `What is the name of Brisbane's main train station?`,
    answers: [
      `A) Central Station`,
      `B) Brisbane City Station`,
      `C) South Bank Station`,
    ],
    correctAnswer: `A) Central Station`,
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: `What is the name of the public transport card used in Brisbane?`,
    answers: [`A) Go Card`, `B) Smart Card`, `C) Metro Card`],
    correctAnswer: `A) Go Card`,
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: `What ferry service operates on the Brisbane River?`,
    answers: [
      `A) Brisbane River Ferries`,
      `B) City Cat Ferries`,
      `C) Brisbane Water Taxis`,
    ],
    correctAnswer: `A) Brisbane River Ferries`,
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: `What type of bike-sharing program is available in Brisbane?`,
    answers: [`A) Free Bike Share`, `B) CityCycle`, `C) Brisbane Bike Network`],
    correctAnswer: `B) CityCycle`,
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question: `What is the most common form of transport in Brisbane?`,
    answers: [`A) Private cars`, `B) Bicycles`, `C) Buses`],
    correctAnswer: `A) Private cars`,
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question: `What is the name of Brisbane's international airport?`,
    answers: [
      `A) Brisbane Airport`,
      `B) Queensland Airport`,
      `C) Gold Coast Airport`,
    ],
    correctAnswer: `A) Brisbane Airport`,
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question: `What is the average distance between Brisbane and Gold Coast?`,
    answers: [`A) 50 km`, `B) 70 km`, `C) 30 km`],
    correctAnswer: `A) 50 km`,
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question: `What is the main bus station in Brisbane?`,
    answers: [
      `A) Brisbane Transit Centre`,
      `B) Fortitude Valley Bus Station`,
      `C) Brisbane Central Bus Station`,
    ],
    correctAnswer: `A) Brisbane Transit Centre`,
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question: `What form of transportation is popular for commuting to the city from the suburbs?`,
    answers: [`A) Carpooling`, `B) Public buses`, `C) Ridesharing`],
    correctAnswer: `B) Public buses`,
  },
];
